

About Me

Hello there I am Karim, a web development professional with 3 years of experience. I have worked on a variety of technical projects that include developing web applications using modern technologies. I have excellent skills in React, Next.js for the client side, Node.js and Express.js For server side, as well as proficiency in JavaScript. I am always striving to develop and improve my technical skills and build great applications that meet the needs of users.



+20 115 599 3133



INFO@KARIMEMAD.COM



Cairo , Giza , EGYPT

Website: https://karimemadhmady.github.io/CV

LANGUAGE

- Proficient in English.
- Arabic Native

SOFT SKILLS

- · project management
- Creativity
- cooperative
- communication skills
- Negotiation
- solving problems
- teamwork skills

LEARN SKILLS NOW

- System design
- SQL, NOSQL
- unit testing

KARIM EMAD

web developer

EXPERIENCE

full stack developer
An internship at wxora company
2023

I am very grateful to have completed the training at Wxora in modern web development as it has greatly enhanced my skills and knowledge

Website developer Eagle Company 2020 - Now

"Collaborating closely with companies to understand their vision and goals for their website is essential to creating a successful, user-friendly user experience design and continuous improvement."

Digital Marketing and SEO clients and owner's business 2021 - Now

"Effective communication and understanding the unique needs and goals of each client is crucial for success in digital marketing."

THE COURSES

- Professional Front-End Web Development ,Udacity
- Hsoub Academy course in web development
- Eng Yehia Al-Arabi's course in modern web development
- · Digital Marketing Professional From Udacity
- Digital Marketing From ICDL Arabia
- Certificate of skills in digital marketing from Google

EDUCATION

Technical diploma

Technical diploma from 2014-2017

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Javascript Next.js
Typescript React.js
CSS Node.js
HTML Express.js
Woo-Commerce Mongodb

WordPress/Shopify/Odoo

SEO

digital marketing